<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SkyScanner</string>
    <string name="image_transition">image%1d</string>
    <string name="world">enjoy with a world</string>
    <string name="overseas">travel over 3 seas</string>
    <string name="stay">Stay at home</string>
    <string name="travel">Travel</string>
    <string name="inpiration">Inpiration</string>
    <string name="trip">Trip</string>
    <string name="inspiration">Inspiration</string>
    <string name="profile">profile</string>
    <string name="profiler">Profile</string>
    <string name="failure">Failure is not an option!</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQs \n \n Question: What is “NASA Solve”? \n \n Answer: Before the NASA Solve website was established, there was no “one-stop-shop” for listing all of the opportunities available to the public to participate in NASA science and technology activities. NASA Solve is a location on the NASA website where individual members of the public can find these opportunities. NASA Solve is an invitation to members of the public to advance research, solve problems, and potentially win prizes as a result of their work. \n \n Question: Why does NASA want the public’s participation? \n \n Answer: NASA has historically sought solutions to challenging research questions and engineering problems by looking within the ranks of its own workforce, the U.S. aerospace industry, academic institutions, and certain other non-governmental organizations. We continue that practice today. But we also recognize that NASA’s work in space and aeronautics continues to be of great interest to the worldwide public and that good ideas can come from anywhere. NASA Solve provides a way for NASA to engage the public’s interest and ingenuity and make space exploration and other avenues of NASA research an endeavor of and by people everywhere. \n \n Question: Who can participate in the opportunities listed on NASA Solve? How do I know what opportunities are right for me? \n \n Answer: NASA Solve is intended as NASA’s gateway to involving more people in the exciting work NASA does in space exploration and aeronautics and Earth science research. The opportunities listed here are intended to attract individuals with a range of interests and skills across a wide age range. Read the descriptions of the projects carefully to determine if the project is a good fit for you or your organization. Eligibility requirements for individual challenge and prize activities are listed on their respective websites, which you can reach through NASA Solve. Note that NASA is prohibited by law from awarding prize funding to entities outside of the United States. \n \n Question: Are the opportunities on NASA Solve suitable for children and school groups? \n \n Answer: NASA is committed to providing students with hands-on science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) learning opportunities. We also seek students’ contributions to helping us address real-world research and technology development needs. You can find opportunities suitable for children and school groups under the “student opportunities” tab on the main NASA Solve page. \n \n Question: Can I get paid for participating in the opportunities listed on NASA Solve? \n \n Answer: NASA has authority from Congress to develop prize competitions in relation to its scientific activities and technology development needs and to award cash prizes for winners. Please review the webpages of the prize competitions that interest you to determine whether and what prize purses may be available and the criteria which NASA will apply to awarding such prizes. \n \n Question: What kinds of participatory opportunities are housed on NASA Solve? Answer: Specific projects listed on this site include crowdsourced challenges and prize competitions, citizen science projects; competitions aimed at advancing student education, and many more activities. \n \n Question: How does NASA define crowdsourcing? \n \n Answer: According to NASA Policy Directive 1090.1, crowdsourcing solicits products, services, ideas, or content contributions from many people, usually (but not necessarily) through the Internet and may result in the making of award(s). Crowdsourcing is different from ordinary outsourcing because a task or problem is outsourced to an undefined public rather than to a specific, named group or individual. \n \n Question: How does NASA define a challenge activity? \n \n Answer: According to NASA Policy Directive 1090.1, challenges use a focused problem-statement approach to obtain solutions and/or stimulate innovation from a broad, sometimes undefined, public rather than a specific, named group or individual. \n \n Question: How does NASA define a prize competition? \n \n Answer: According to NASA Policy Directive 1090.1, prize competitions competitively award prizes to stimulate innovation in a manner that has the potential to advance the mission of NASA. \n \n Question: How does NASA define citizen science? \n \n Answer: NASA uses the definition of citizen science which appears on the U.S. Government’s central citizen science website, www.citizenscience.gov This definition takes citizen science to be activities in which the public participates voluntarily in the scientific process, addressing real-world problems in ways that may include formulating research questions, conducting scientific experiments, collecting and analyzing data, interpreting results, making new discoveries, developing technologies and applications, and solving complex problems. \n \n Question: An opportunity in which I was interested is no longer posted on NASA Solve! Why not? \n \n Answer: How long an opportunity remains posted on NASA Solve depends on the activity’s duration. Some of our projects remain active for years, e.g., when scientists have a great deal of spacecraft data available for the public to help analyze. Challenge and prize competitions often have specific close dates and consider only the entries they receive prior to then. The close dates are posted for each of the opportunities listed on NASA Solve, so please check carefully those that interest you. \n \n Question: Is there a way to get notified when new opportunities to participate with NASA become available? Answer: New opportunities are created regularly, so please check NASA Solve often! Also, please follow us on Twitter at @NASASolve as we often announce new opportunities that way, too. \n \n Question: My organization runs a participatory activity. Can I list in on NASA Solve? \n \n Answer: NASA only posts opportunities where NASA has a formal funding or partnering role with the activity. If you believe your activity meets this criterion, please contact us. \n \n Question: I’m a federal employee and I have an idea for a challenge or prize competition that I would like to run. Who do I contact? \n \n Answer: We’d love to help you run your first challenge. Please reach out to us and we’ll help to get you started. NASA’s Center of Excellence for Collaborative Innovation (CoECI) is available to assist federal agencies with designing their own challenges and prize competitions. Please visit COECI’s webpage (www.nasa.gov/coeci) or email CoECI for more information. \n \n Question: I love the opportunities available on NASA Solve so much that I would like to start a career in NASA research and technology development! How do I get a job with NASA? \n \n Answer: While NASA Solve invites members of the public to participate voluntarily in research tasks or technology development opportunities, we recognize you may be looking to do even more with NASA. Please check USAJobs.gov regularly for NASA job opportunities.</string>
    <string name="terms">Media Usage Guidelines \n \n NASA Logo\n \n The NASA Insignia , the NASA Logotype and the NASA Seal may not be used for any purpose without explicit permission. These images may not be used by persons who are not NASA employees or on products, publications or web pages that are not NASA-sponsored. These images may not be used to imply endorsement or support of any external organization, program, effort, or persons. \n \n NASA Insignia, Logotype and Seal should not be used as branding devices, or used in or for advertising, trade dress, promotions, or similar marketing purposes, on third-party websites or communications material. \n \n Still Images, Audio Recordings, Video, and Related Computer Files for Non-Commercial Use \n \n NASA content - images, audio, video, and computer files used in the rendition of 3-dimensional models, such as texture maps and polygon data in any format - generally are not subject to copyright in the United States. You may use this material for educational or informational purposes, including photo collections, textbooks, public exhibits, computer graphical simulations and Internet Web pages. This general permission extends to personal Web pages. \n \n News outlets, schools, and text-book authors may use NASA content without needing explicit permission, subject to compliance with these guidelines. NASA content used in a factual manner that does not imply endorsement may be used without needing explicit permission. NASA should be acknowledged as the source of the material. NASA occasionally uses copyright-protected material of third parties with permission on its website. Those images will be marked identified as copyright protected with the name of the copyright holder. NASA\'s use does not convey any rights to others to use the same material. Those wishing to use copyright protected material of third parties must contact the copyright holder directly. \n \n NASA has extensive image and video galleries online, including historic images, current missions, astronomy pictures, Earth images and ways to search for NASA images. Generally, each mission and program has a video and image collection on the topic page. For example, Space Station videos can be found at https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/station/videos/index.html. Content can also be found on our extensive social media channels. \n \n For questions about specific images, please call 202-358-1900. For questions about specific video, please call 202-358-0309. \n NASA Content Used for Commercial Purposes \n \n For more information on using NASA content for commercial purposes, please read NASA Advertising Guidelines and Merchandise Guidelines. Any questions regarding use of NASA content, or any NASA emblems, should be directed to Bert Ulrich in NASA\'s Office of Communications at NASA Headquarters in Washington. \n \n For information on NASA involvement in documentaries and films, please see documentary and fictional film project guidelines. \n \n For use of NASA images in books, clearances may be necessary for images that include any NASA logos or NASA employees to be used as cover art or in promotional content. Otherwise, NASA imagery can be generally used editorially within published works that are not promotional in nature. \n \n If the NASA material is to be used for commercial purposes, including advertisements, it must not explicitly or implicitly convey NASA\'s endorsement of commercial goods or services. \n \n If a NASA image includes an identifiable person, using the image for commercial purposes may infringe that person\'s right of privacy or publicity, and permission should be obtained from the person. \n \n Current NASA employees, including astronauts, may not appear in advertising, promotional, or similar commercial material. \n Commercials and promotional content cannot be filmed on NASA property. \n Linking to NASA Web Sites \n \n NASA Web sites may be linked to from other Web sites, including individuals\' personal Web sites, without explicit permission from NASA. However, such links may not explicitly or implicitly convey NASA\'s endorsement of commercial goods or services. NASA images may be used as graphic to NASA Web sites, provided they are used within the guidelines above. This permission does not extend to use of the NASA Insignia, the NASA Logotype or the NASA Seal. NASA should be acknowledged as the source of the material. \n \n Restrictions \n \n As a government entity, NASA does not license the use of NASA materials nor sign licensing agreements. The agency generally has no objection to the reproduction and use of materials it has made available to the public (audio transmissions and recordings; video transmissions and recording; or still and motion picture photography), subject to the following conditions: \n \n NASA material may not be used to state or imply the endorsement by NASA or by any NASA employee of a commercial product, service, or activity, or used in any manner that might mislead. Please see NASA Advertising Guidelines and Merchandising Guidelines for more information. \n \n It is unlawful to falsely claim copyright or other rights in NASA material. \n \n NASA shall in no way be liable for any costs, expenses, claims, or demands arising out of the use of NASA material by a recipient or a recipient\'s distributees. \n \n NASA does not indemnify nor hold harmless users of NASA material, nor release such users from copyright infringement, nor grant exclusive use rights with respect to NASA material. \n \n If copyright is indicated on any NASA materials, permission should be obtained from the indicated copyright owner prior to use. Subject to any such copyright indications, and subject to compliance with these guidelines, NASA material may be reproduced and distributed without further permission from NASA. \n \n If a recognizable former or Non-NASA person (e.g., a former astronaut or non-NASA talent) appears in NASA content, use of this content for commercial or promotional purposes may infringe on the person’s right of privacy or publicity. Permission should be obtained from the recognizable person in those instances. \n \n Some NASA audiovisual material may incorporate music or footage, which is copyrighted and licensed for the particular NASA work. Any further use by a third party of such material would require permission of the copyright owner. \n \n NASA audiovisual material may include visible NASA identifiers (e.g., the name of the vehicle and the NASA Insignia or Logotype in photographs or film footage of ground vehicles, aircraft or spacecraft). Use of such materials is generally non-objectionable, provided the NASA identifiers appear in their factual context. \n \n Documentary and Fictional Film Project Guidelines NASA participates in scores of documentaries annually and a number of feature films as well. Participation ranges from providing imagery and footage to permitting on-site filming. Below describes the process of working with NASA on documentary and film projects. \n \n Documentaries \n \n NASA works only on projects which have a broadcaster/distributor and funding in place (beyond speculative phase). Once a project has a broadcaster/distributor and funding, NASA must review a treatment to determine NASA involvement and the scope of participation. Treatments can be submitted directly to bert.ulrich@nasa.gov \n \n NASA does not accommodate sizzle reel productions. \n \n NASA does provide publicly available film footage and imagery regardless of involvement in a particular production. This use is subject to these Media Usage Guidelines and the Advertising Guidelines. \n \n NASA does not fund external documentary projects. \n \n For interviews for documentaries, a release form is not required. \n \n Feature film and fictional film projects \n \n NASA participates only in projects which have funding and distribution in place. \n \n A formal agreement is often required when there is a need to lay out what is expected of both parties in terms of shoots, clearances, protection of NASA\'s appearance in a fictional storyline, etc. An agreement may also be needed when the parties plan for an on-going collaboration for education or outreach activities beyond routine appearances or interviews. \n \n After providing a signed NASA Acknowledgment of Non-Disclosure, if necessary, NASA then reviews a script to assess participation in a project. In cases where NASA participation is approved, other items may need to be addressed, including: review and clearance for use of the NASA Insignia and other identifiers, footage, still imagery and other NASA assets; details of any filming on NASA property; post assistance; and when appropriate, outreach leading to release of the film. \n \n NASA does provide publicly available film footage and imagery regardless of any direct NASA involvement in a particular production. This use is subject to these Media Usage Guidelines and Advertising Guidelines. \n \n Commercial and promotional shoots \n \n NASA does not permit shooting of promotional content such as television spots, commercials, etc. at NASA facilities. In some cases, filming can take place at an outside NASA visitor center run by a commercial entity. Please refer to Advertising Guidelines for more information. \n \n For more information, please contact Bert Ulrich at bert.ulrich@nasa.gov Communications Partnerships \n \n In addition to TV/film collaborations, NASA’s Office of Communications sometimes enters into partnerships with organizations to support external projects that help tell NASA’s story or inspire interest in space and STEM careers. NASA generally supports projects that have the ability to reach large numbers of the public or non-traditional audiences, expanding our efforts beyond of the aerospace community. \n \n For more information, please contact Maureen O’Brien at Maureen.Obrien-1@nasa.gov \n \n Anniversary Logos \n \n Anniversary logos are permitted on merchandise through the approval process cited in the Merchandising Guidelines. \n \n</string>
    <string name="privacy"><![CDATA[Privacy Policy \n \n This notice provides NASA\'s policy regarding the nature, purpose, use and sharing of any information collected via this Web site. The information you provide on a NASA Web site will be used only for its intended purpose. We will protect your information consistent with the principles of the Privacy Act, the e-Government act of 2002, the Federal Records Act, and as applicable, the Freedom of Information Act. \n \n Submitting information is strictly voluntary. By doing so, you are giving NASA your permission to use the information for the intended purpose. If you do not want to give NASA permission to use your information, simply do not provide it. However, not providing certain information may result in NASA\'s inability to provide you with the information or services you desire. \n \n There are several types of information we collect. These include: \n Automatically Collected Information \n Information Collected for Tracking and Customization (Cookies) \n Personal Information \n Information from Children\n Information maintained within Privacy Act Systems of Records\n NASA will only share your information with another government agency if it relates to that agency, or as otherwise required by law. We may share information with private organizations as part of a service that provides NASA.gov users with increased capabilities or functionality on the site. NASA never creates individual profiles. \n \n Automatically Collected Information \n \n This website uses Google Analytics Premium. Please refer to the following policies on Google\'s website for more information: \n Google\'s main privacy policy \n Cookies & Google Analytics on Websites \n Opt out of Google Analytics Cookies \n We collect and temporarily store certain technical information about your visit for use in site management and security purposes. This information includes: \n \n The Internet domain from which you access our Web site (for example, if you use a private Internet access account, or if you connect from an educational domain); \n The IP address (a unique number for each computer connected to the Internet) from which you access our Web site; \n The type of browser (e.g., Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer) used to access our site; \n The operating system (Windows, Mac) used to access our site; \n The date and time you access our site; \n The URLs of the pages you visit; \n Your username, if it was used to log in to the Web site; and \n If you visited this NASA Web site from another Web site, the URL of the forwarding site. \n Anonymous summary demographic information about our visitors such as gender, age range, and areas of interest for adults over the age of 18. We do this by using Google Demographic and Interests reports. When you visit a website that has partnered with the Google Display Network, Google stores a number in your browser using a persistent cookie to remember your visits. This number uniquely identifies a web browser, not a specific person. Browsers may be associated with a demographic category, such as gender or age range, based on the sites that were visited. This demographic information is used to help us better understand our visitors\' interests and needs to more effectively develop content to serve you. \n \n This information is generally used to help us make our site more useful for you. With this data we learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. Although the primary purpose of automatically collecting this kind of information is not to track individuals who visit this site, in certain circumstances and consistent with Federal law, NASA may take additional steps to identify you using this information and may share this information, including your identity, with other agencies. \n \n Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are retained temporarily as required for security and site management purposes only. \n \n Information Collected for Tracking and Customization (Cookies) \n \n A cookie is a small file that a Web site transfers to your computer to allow it to remember specific information about your session while you are connected. Your computer will only share the information in the cookie with the Web site that provided it, and no other Web site can request it. There are two types of cookies, session and persistent. Session cookies last only as long as your Web browser is open. Once you close your browser, the cookie disappears. Persistent cookies store information on your computer for longer periods of time. \n \n NASA Web sites may use session cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through the site, or to allow you to customize your preferences for interacting with the site. A few NASA Web sites may also make use of persistent cookies to remember you between visits so, for example, you can save your customized preference settings for future visits. Each NASA site using persistent cookies identifies itself as doing so. If you do not wish to have session or persistent cookies stored on your machine, you can turn them off in your browser. However, this may affect the functioning of some NASA Web sites. \n \n Providing Information to Third Parties \n \n NASA may share information with private organizations as part of a service that provides NASA users with increased capabilities or functionality on the site. On www.nasa.gov, the function at the top of each page is provided by a third party, AddThis. This firm collects information on visitors who use this feature to share NASA content on their Facebook pages, Twitter feeds or other social media or social networking sites. As noted in their privacy policy AddThis uses this information for its own business purposes, including marketing the information to other parties. \n \n AddThis does not collect information from users who do not use the feature. \n \n Personal Information \n \n If you choose to provide us with personal information, through such methods as completing a form or sending us an email, we will use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information or services you have requested. \n \n Remember that email isn\'t necessarily secure. You should never send sensitive or personal information like your Social Security number in an email. Use postal mail or secure Web sites instead. \n Some of our Web sites ask visitors who request specific information to fill out a registration form. For example, vendors looking for marketing opportunities by visiting our NASA Acquisition Internet Service site may be asked to register to obtain email notices of business opportunities. Other information collected at Web sites through questionnaires, feedback forms, or other means, enables us to determine visitors\' interests, with the goal of providing better service to our customers. \n Linking Policy and Disclaimer of Endorsement \n \n NASA links to many Web sites created and maintained by other public and/or private organizations. NASA provides links to these sites as a service to our users. The presence of a link is not a NASA endorsement of the site. \n When users follow a link to an outside Web site, they are leaving NASA and are subject to the privacy and security policies of the owners/sponsors of the outside Web site(s). NASA is not responsible for the information collection practices of non-NASA sites.]]></string>
    <string name="here_collected_all_information_and_articles_about_nasa_and_our_mission">Here collected , all information and articles about NASA and our mission</string>
    <string name="oops_something_went_wrong">oops something went wrong!</string>
</resources>